today we have got a topic that could
save your dream vacation travel
insurance I know insurance
but hear me out I have a real life
incident that happened with two of my
friends on a vacation and travel
insurance actually saved them
hit the Subscribe button and let's get
started
so my two very good friends sonali and
Karthik had been planning this once in a
lifetime trip to Bali since year setting
up every penny they can for this trip
right
so finally the day comes and they are on
this enchanting island of Bali right
there's Sun soap beaches and beautiful
and they were exploring the local
markets they were excluding the Exotic
Cuisines our sun set up my phone may
capture and it was magical for them but
yeah
and then on a sunny afternoon apparently
they were going for a swimming while
sonali got tangled in some coral and she
got a deep cut on her leg and was
bleeding quite a lot now these people
before coming to their travel somebody
in their relatives advised them to get
travel insurance before they left India
so Karthik immediately
the insurance company arranged for an
ambulance rushed sonali to the nearest
hospital and made sure she received
export Medical Care over there
the insurance company covered all the
expenses that were there the treatment
the tests the medication everything was
covered friends here is a crucial
takeaway
firstly travel insurance is a safety net
against unforeseen circumstances so it
deals with emergencies medical
emergencies it deals with trip
cancellations it deals with a lost
baggage
secondly it gives you a peace of mind
having your travel insurance always
gives you that mental peace and you can
really enjoy and thirdly it's a plan for
the unexpected right so just Insurance
prepares you for what might come
make sure travel insurance is a
non-negotiable part of your planning
it's your one-way ticket to a worry-free
adventure
thank you for joining us today if you
found this video helpful don't forget to
give it a thumbs up and share this
content with your fellow Travelers until
next time safe travels and remember your
adventure deserves protection gain that
travel insurance
thank you
[Music]